# **AMY PASTORIUS**

Phone: 612-269-0708 | Email: PAST0073@UMN.EDU | Address: 150 Snelling Ave North St Paul, MN 55104

GitHub: https://github.com/past0073 | Partfalia: https://past0073.github.io/02-Homework/

Linkedln: https://www.linkedin.com/in/amy-pastorius-609324157/

#### SUMMARY

Strategic Nonprofit Manager with experience in maintaining key customer relationships, resource and inventory management, and implementing process improvement. Extensive education in full stack web development including javaScript, jQuery, node.js, and proficient in managing GitHub repositories. Interested in continuing career in management and specializing in responsive web development.

#### **TECHNICAL SKILLS & EXPERTISE**

- Management Office365 Applications Web Development Customer Relationship Management Windows® QuickBooks
- javaScript jQuery JSON Node.js HTML CSS Bootstrap / Tailwind Ajax GitHub Visual Studio Code Slack •

### EXPERIENCE

AccessAbility, Inc. | Minneapolis, MN

**Operations & Production Manager** 

2020 - Present

- Manage key accounts and customer relationships
- Ensure the on-time delivery of high-quality finished goods
- · Lead business administration activities: inventory management, purchasing, and material sourcing
- Forecast and conduct market research

AccessAbility, Inc. | Minneapolis, MN

**Program Services Supervisor** 

2019 - 2020

- Managed and mentored four case management professionals
- Collaborated with clients, social workers, and caregivers
- Ensured licensing and CARF accreditation compliance standards
- Earned 2019 Employee of the Year

AccessAbility, Inc. | Minneapolis, MN

Case Manager

2015 - 2019

- Managed a caseload of 35-40 individuals
- Provided on-site job coaching
- Created support plans to help individuals served meet their employment goals
- Earned Award of Excellence in 2016.

## EDUCATION

UNIVERSITY OF MINNESOTA | Online

**JUNE 2021** 

**Full Stack Web Development Certificate** 

UNIVERSITY OF MINNESOTA | TWIN CITIES, MN
Bachelor of Arts, Speech-Language-Hearing Sciences

MAY 2015